It's cold in here
Scent path
The sound of wind Or a distant
Empty machine The
door is closed, the lock is set
The first time I'm alone
This quiet is a heavy sheet
On this bed that's not my own
My laptop's dark, the plug's too high A
world I cannot reach
Simple task I cannot do
Lesson she won't teach
Real college kid That's what she said to me
You're not all living on your own But I can't even
get free I'm stranded in these denim clothes My
shoes are on the floor I'm a real college kid And I
can't find the door The rain begins to tap the
glass
A cold and lonely sound
I have a bag of sandwiches I'm
trapped here on my own
She never taught me how to change
She never taught me how to talk
You never really taught me How to say goodbye
Real college kid That's what she said to me Good
old living on your own But I can't even get free
I'm stranded in these denim clothes My shoes are
on the floor I'm a real college kid And I can't
find the door What if she was right? What if I just
failed? A silly college experiment This
academic jail I wanna go home I'm not ready, I'm
not
I'm a real college kid That's what she said to me
You're not all living on your own But I can't even
get free I'm stranded in these denim clothes My
shoes are on the floor I'm a real college kid And I
can't find the door
Living on my
Living on my own All alone